<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
 
 <title>Anup's Blog</title>
 <link href="http://anupsahoo.github.io/blog/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://anupsahoo.github.io/blog"/>
 <updated>2020-06-04T16:02:40+05:30</updated>
 <id>http://anupsahoo.github.io/blog</id>
 <author>
   <name>Anup Sahoo</name>
   <email>anup.aksahoo@gmail.com</email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>Choosing Tests Strategy </title>
   <link href="http://anupsahoo.github.io/blog/2020/04/28/anup-sahoo-choosing-testing_statergy"/>
   <updated>2020-04-28T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
   <id>http://anupsahoo.github.io//blog/2020/04/28/anup-sahoo-choosing-testing_statergy</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;what-is-test-strategy&quot;&gt;What is Test Strategy?&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A Test strategy describes the testing approach of the software development cycle by
providing the generic test entry criteria &amp;amp; exit criteria for each level and the relationship
among the levels from a Quality Assurance perspective.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-is-the-objective-of-test-strategy&quot;&gt;What is the Objective of Test Strategy?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To understand overall target by managing the Product &amp;amp; Project risk. Here, We
mentioned the different levels of test strategies and high-level activities associated with
it to serve you well for the long term.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;how-many-types-of-test-strategies-and-where-to-use&quot;&gt;How many types of Test Strategies and where to use?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our Test Strategies are broadly categorized under the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Analytical Strategies&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Model-Based Strategies&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Methodical Strategies&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Process/Standard Compliant Strategies&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Reactive Strategies&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Consultative Strategies&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Regression Averse Strategies&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;analytical-strategy&quot;&gt;Analytical Strategy:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is a Risk based testing. At this level of testing, Test team analyses the test basis to
identify the test conditions to cover.
Derive the test conditions from the requirements Design the tests and implement to
cover the conditions Execute the tests based on the priority of requirement covered by
each test to determine the order in which the tests will be run. Test results will be
reported in terms of requirement status as follows:
• Requirement tested and passed&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Requirement tested and failed&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Requirement not yet fully tested.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Requirement testing blocked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;model-based-strategy&quot;&gt;Model Based Strategy:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At this level, Test team develops a Model of a system environment like input
conditions to which system is subjected and How the system should behave? Test team
also develops model for ideal, expected &amp;amp; minimum throughput rates, response time
and resource allocation by considering the current product environment Hardware,
Software, Data Capacity, Network and Infrastructure.
It can be used for testing Operational Profiling such as to test the performance of a fast
growing mobile device application.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;methodical-strategies&quot;&gt;Methodical Strategies:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These strategies are Quality Characteristic Based. At this level of testing, the Test team
uses a Predetermined set of test conditions such as a Quality Standard,
Checklist/Collection of Generalised and logical test conditions which subject to a
particular Domain type of testing/ Application testing. Test team uses the set of test
conditions from one iteration to next or from release to next.
It can be used to test the Maintenance of a simple, stable e-commerce website by using
the checklist that identifies the key functions, attributes and link for each page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;processstandard-compliant-strategies&quot;&gt;Process/Standard Compliant Strategies:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At this level of testing, Test team follows a set of process should address
Documentation, Proper Identification, Use of Test Basis &amp;amp; Test Oracle(s) and an
organization of Test Team defined by a standard committee or other panel of experts.
It can be used to test the projects following Scrum Agile Management Techniques by
analyses the user stories that describe particular features, estimates the test effort as
part of the planning process for the iteration, identify the test conditions for each user 
story and finally execute the test &amp;amp; report the status of each story during the time of
execution.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;reactive-strategies&quot;&gt;Reactive Strategies:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At this level of testing, Test team wait to design and implement tests until the software is
received and reacted to an actual system under test. Testers periodically report results
of the testing session to the Test Manager.
It can be used for Defect Based Attacks such as an exploratory testing on Menu based
application. In this, A set of test charters including features, menu selections and
screens to be developed respectively. Each tester is assigned to a set of test charters to
structure their exploratory testing sessions by using the charters.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;consultative-strategies&quot;&gt;Consultative Strategies:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At this level, Test team relies on the Input of one or more key stake holders to
Determine the test conditions to cover. It can be used as User -Directed testing such as
to test the outsourcing compatibility for Web Based Applications, Company will provide
the list of browser versions, Anti-Malware software, Operating System connection types
and other configurations to test service provider that they want to evaluate against the
application. The testing service provider can use these techniques such as Pairwise
Testing for high priority options and Equivalence Partitioning for low priority options to
generate the tests.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;regression--aversion-testing-strategies&quot;&gt;Regression- Aversion Testing Strategies:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At this level of testing, Test team uses various techniques to manage the Risk of
Regression especially Functional and/or Non-Functional Regression test automation at
one or more levels.
It can be used as Extensive Automation by using GUI based test
automation tool to automate The typical and exception use cases for Web
Based Applications. Those tests are then executed at any time the
application is modified.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;how-to-choose&quot;&gt;How To Choose?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The selection of specific test strategy should be appropriate to an organization Needs
and Means. Different test strategies are suitable for different organizations and projects.
Test strategy also differs from the various development models. An organization may
tailor test strategies to make it suitable for a particular operation and project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-are-the-advantages&quot;&gt;What are the Advantages?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The test Strategy also describe the following.:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Test Strategy should define the testing tools like Test Management, Defect
Management Systems and Automated Test Tools.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Test Strategy identify the data that will be recorded, Test Measurement and Test
Control. The data will be reported to show the progress of testing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Test Strategy also describe the Integration procedures, Test specification
techniques, independence of testing, mandatory and optional standards,
configuration management approach and reusability of software and test work
products.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Note: While designing Test Strategy one should be consider the required test
environment&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Magic Methods In python </title>
   <link href="http://anupsahoo.github.io/blog/2020/03/28/anup-sahoo-python-magic_methods00"/>
   <updated>2020-03-28T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
   <id>http://anupsahoo.github.io//blog/2020/03/28/anup-sahoo-python-magic_methods00</id>
   <content type="html">
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Magic Methods In python </title>
   <link href="http://anupsahoo.github.io/blog/2020/03/28/anup-sahoo-python-magic_methods0"/>
   <updated>2020-03-28T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
   <id>http://anupsahoo.github.io//blog/2020/03/28/anup-sahoo-python-magic_methods0</id>
   <content type="html">
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Magic Methods In python </title>
   <link href="http://anupsahoo.github.io/blog/2020/03/28/anup-sahoo-python-magic_methods"/>
   <updated>2020-03-28T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
   <id>http://anupsahoo.github.io//blog/2020/03/28/anup-sahoo-python-magic_methods</id>
   <content type="html">
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Python Control Flow</title>
   <link href="http://anupsahoo.github.io/blog/2020/03/27/anup-sahoo-python-control-flow"/>
   <updated>2020-03-27T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
   <id>http://anupsahoo.github.io//blog/2020/03/27/anup-sahoo-python-control-flow</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;hello-world&quot;&gt;Hello World&lt;/h2&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Data Types In python </title>
   <link href="http://anupsahoo.github.io/blog/2020/03/15/anup-sahoo-python-data_types"/>
   <updated>2020-03-15T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
   <id>http://anupsahoo.github.io//blog/2020/03/15/anup-sahoo-python-data_types</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Data types are data items that represents the type of value that tells what operations 
can be performed on a particular data.Since everything is an object in Python,data types
are actually classes and variables are instance (object) of these classes. Below are the
 standard data type of Python:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Numeric&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sequence Type&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Boolean&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Set&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Dictionary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;numeric-&quot;&gt;Numeric :&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Numeric data type that represent the data which has numeric value. Numeric value can be 
integer, floating number or complex numbers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;integers&quot;&gt;Integers:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This value is represented by int class. It contains positive or negative 
whole numbers (without fraction or decimal). In Python there is no limit to how long 
an integer value can be. Example :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;blockquote&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;a = 5&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/blockquote&gt;

  &lt;blockquote&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;type(a)&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/blockquote&gt;

  &lt;blockquote&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;class ‘int’&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;float-&quot;&gt;Float :&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This value is represented by float class. It is a real number with floating 
 point representation. It is specified by a decimal point. Example :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;blockquote&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;a = 5.6&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/blockquote&gt;

  &lt;blockquote&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;type(a)&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;blockquote&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;class ‘float’&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;complex-numbers-&quot;&gt;Complex Numbers :&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Complex number is represented by complex class&amp;amp; specified as (real part) + 
 (imaginary part)j. For example :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Example :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;blockquote&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;a = 5.6+4j&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/blockquote&gt;

  &lt;blockquote&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;type(a)&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/blockquote&gt;

  &lt;blockquote&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;class ‘complex’&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;sequence-type&quot;&gt;Sequence Type&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;boolean&quot;&gt;Boolean&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;set&quot;&gt;Set&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;dictionary&quot;&gt;Dictionary&lt;/h2&gt;

</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>About Python and Its Installation</title>
   <link href="http://anupsahoo.github.io/blog/2020/03/14/anup-sahoo-Python_Basics"/>
   <updated>2020-03-14T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
   <id>http://anupsahoo.github.io//blog/2020/03/14/anup-sahoo-Python_Basics</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;hello-world&quot;&gt;Hello World&lt;/h2&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 
</feed>
